Oh my God!!! It's a cave!
It's a secret cave!
We've come a long way!
You know, Mr. Meimei...
He bought you, too.
Let's be friends.
Yumi!
Hello.
I'm Kaho Fujishima, a student of NUTAZAKA 464.
I'm going to celebrate my first anniversary with Mei Higashimura,
I'd like to participate in LALA.
I'm so excited, I really couldn't sleep at all last night,
Mei always takes the lead at times like this.
Last time I didn't hand over the mirror.
When I was thinking about it...
She gave me the mirror and said, 'Here, use this'.
She's a really nice person who can take care of little things like that.
I'm sure she will be able to show you a wonderful year today too.
I'm sure I'll be able to show you all a wonderful year.
Taxi ride!
Putting on the chute belt.
How did you come to this opportunity today?
I thought I'd like to go out with Colin.
I wanted to go out with Colin, and I wanted to go to Nana, my home town.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy to go with you.
I'm so happy.
We're going to a place now.
I don't know what a place is.
I'm going to recommend a place.
Cream.
You like sweet things.
I like it a lot.
It's sweet.
Yeah!
Where you can eat it.
Me too.
Where I've been.
It's lovely, you know, when it's pretty and you can eat it in all sorts of places. Where I've seen it too,
It's cute.
I've been to places where you can see installations in the neckties.
You can see installations in those places too.
It's nice. Really.
Yay!
Here we are. Here.
The pudding dominie.
Have you seen this place?
Have you been here?
It's really here.
Mr. Swedish.
Around here.
Convenience centre.
I saw the photo.
I'm so happy.
Yay.
Swedish pilgrimage.
It's so cute.
Ja ja ja ja. Dotcom!
Dotcom!
It's so cute.
Cute.
Every part of it is cute.
Wow! Asahi!
Super cute.
There are all kinds of puddings.
Yes, there are. Something like Daibutsu, like Daibutsu,
Yes, that's right.
The Daibutsu pudding is famous,
Oh!
Yes, there is.
What flavour is it?
Pudding.
I've never seen it before.
This is so big.
Enough pudding for a year.
Enough for a year.
Looks delicious. What do you think?
Eh, it's fine. Thank you. I'm sorry, it looks good for the first year.
Eh, is it OK? Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Do you want to review the pudding?
Curry.
Marshmallow custard.
Marshmallow custard, I presume.
Okay, pudding, two custard puddings, please.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Yay.
Eh, what's this?
Wow. And it's a hiragana zelkova.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
It's amazing. It's a cave.
This is a secret house.
There's a room that really looks like a secret house.
Really. It's a secret house! There's a room that really looks like a secret room.
Really? That's a false mouth!
But we don't eat here.
We never eat here.
Where do you eat?
Nara Park.
Wow! Nara Park! I'm so happy!
It's so cute!
Get in, Kaho.
It's a huge swing.
Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
Yay.
Wow.
That's great.
Look, there's a Kamoki over there. We'll be waiting for you.
We're here, we're in Nara Park.
Oh, my God.
There are deer.
Almost as many as people.
There are as many deer as people.
What are they doing now?
I'm in the middle of something.
I want some pudding around here.
Aah!
Ooh!
Whoa! Wah!
It's coming round and round and round.
Whoa! Hold on!
Whoa! Wait!
Oh, no.
Oh, you're not scared?
Yeah, I'm scared when they come near me, but...
Yeah, I'm afraid.
I won't do anything.
Okay, okay.
Oh, I'll come, I'll come, I'll be scared if a warm grandpa comes, but I won't do anything.
Are you scared? I'm a bit scared.
Oh, I found a bench!
Wow, that's kind of a pussycat.
It's not like a tease, is it?
Choo-choo-choo.
I said "occhan-choko".
Popsicle.
The pudding we just had.
Yay!
Let's eat.
I'll have some pudding.
What if it's not normal?
I got a spoon.
Yay, thank you!
I'll open it.
A plate.
This is my sister's. Thank you.
Here's your sister's thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Sounds good.
Delicious!
It tastes like a big Buddha.
I see.
That's great.
What if a deer comes after the pudding?
That could happen.
Wait, look, it's eating the pudding!
Oh, that deer is dangerous.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, wait, look, it's eating the pudding.
Oh, that deer, that's not good.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I knew it was food-sensitive.
Do you want to give it a name?
Name it.
Yumi.
Yumi, Yumi.
Scary, scary, scary.
Yumi and Yumi.
Yumi the idiot.
The duo.
Delicious.
Good.
This is delicious! Good! What's this?
Yum! I've got it! Yes!
Oh, it's delicious.
Oh, help me.
Uh-oh!
Se-see!
Whoa!
She escorted me.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, thank you, I'm going to go buy some deer crackers.
Excuse me, I'd like to give you some deer crackers.
Oh, here you go.
Wow.
Senbei-san bought me some deer crackers.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I got the deer crackers.
I'm going to give them to you.
I'll give you this.
Look at this! Look!
I don't know, I don't know, I'm looking.
Here we go.
There's really, really no one here.
Oh, isn't that fast? Deer, so fast.
Wait a minute, I'm scared.
What do we do, what do we do?
Wait, wait, something's coming!
I'm scared, aren't I? Something's coming! Aah! I'm scared!
Hey, help! Aaah! There's so many!
Um, Meimei bought this for me.
Ha-ha-ha!
We all loved it.
It's the Dramaworkers' Act.
They were all bought by Meimei.
Drama method.
Mr. Meimei bought it for me.
So popular! Kajolins are very popular!
She put her feet on it, but it's a very popular kajolina! Very popular! Risa-san bought it for me, and she put her feet on it.
I know how much it's worth.
Do you?
I'm already crying.
You're all crying.
Wow, I don't have one.
Wait a minute.
I really want to keep it.
Oh, I think I can.
Here you go!
Oh, my God!
Oh, wait a minute!
You can't come this way, can you?
Are you coming?
Wait a minute!
Are you finished?
It's over, the deer.
Oh, my God, what's going on?
Scary, scary, scary, scary, scary.
Oh!
It was gone in an instant.
That was quick.
That's great.
Kajolins really ate my skirt.
Oh, that's terrible, isn't it?
There was a shuka once who ate so much.
She won't eat my skirt.
She loves Kajolins.
Everyone was telling Kajolins about it.
She was really good at giving them gifts.
Let's go and buy some souvenirs.
Wow, they sell all sorts of stuff.
I want to buy something to go with it.
Are you sure?
I'd love to buy some. Are you sure? Congratulations.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm Fukui.
It's nice and practical, that's for sure.
When we were doing some kind of stretching at the concert...
I remember you looking at my socks when I was stretching at the concert.
I remember.
I said I had some, too.
I was like, "You have these?
And I was like...
I remember she looked at my socks and said, "Do you have these? I'm with you, with the bag and the fruit, do you have this?
No, it's quite common.
Like bags.
Actually, they are the same.
Yes, it's really cute.
I'll take this one.
Bye-bye, bye-bye. Yay! I'll take this one, it was a snap check!
Bye-bye, deer!
Bye-bye! Thank you very much for saying bye-bye to all the deer!
Thank you very much.
Next time we'll go somewhere a bit tin... tin...
Next time we'll go somewhere a bit cooler. Yay!
There is one in Sapporo. This kind of place.
Is there? Is there?
It's called Tanuki Mineji.
Really?
There are raccoon dog figurines and such, aren't there?
Those tanuki?
Like a ghost tanuki.
Not a cute tanuki, but an ornament.
Not the usual ones, but, you know, the ones from the Koseki shop.
That's it, isn't it?
I want to go to Sapporo. Something like the Sapporo Snow Festival.
Yes, I have.
Have you been to that one?
It's amazing, I want to go.
Like a primary school?
I'd like to go to a primary school.
Oh, really? I heard there are others. All of them.
Famous.
That's nice.
I really want to go.
I'd love to be there on the 20th, please, Part 2.
Let's go to Hokkaido for the second part.
Let's go.
This is it!
That's what I'm talking about!
It's here!
Bon appétit, bon appétit, bon appétit, bon appétit, bon appétit, bon appétit, bon appétit!
Bon appétit!
Nara is famous for shaved ice!
Really? Really?
So, yes.
And I, for one...
I like eating shaved ice
I like having shaved ice.
Oh, no.
Really?
I'm really looking forward to it.
What? Choosing the menu.
Yes, sir.
What?
Are you serious?
No, no, no.
Oh, look.
Oh, it says "berry berry" on it.
Where does it say that?
Look, it's got a berry berry gruffer.
That's right.
I think I'll have this one.
Oh, this one looks like a photo, too.
Employee chain.
Like this one.
Wow, oh my God, the menu, this one looks like a photo too Shine Kiwi, let's put this in!
Oh, no!
It's red bean paste!
I'll have the Shine Kiwi.
I'll have a Shine Kiwi.
Shine kiwi yoghurt and berry berry yoghurt, please.
Sure.
Thank you.
Yes, please.
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Thank you.
I'm really going all out today.
I'm really crammed with beauty.
I've done so many things and bought new cosmetics.
Oh, no...
I'm really going hard today.
But at the beauty parlour, this is today's level that everyone was a bit too concerned about.
Wow, they're already here.
It's early.
Millimetre by millimetre.
Yes, yes.
It's still hot, so please go this way.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Fish growth.
Well then. Here it comes - it's hot, so I'll take it this way. Yes, I'll take it. Fish harley.
Yes, thank you.
Here it is.
What do you think?
Cute.
If you say it's cute,
It's cute.
It looks really delicious.
Let's eat.
First, I'm going to eat the starter.
How is it? How does it taste?
Tafumi makes pasta.
It came out of my face.
Yo! It came out of my face! Yay!
Bon appétit.
Yes!
Yum!
Hmm!
What's this?
Oh, my God!
Sweet!
Whoa!
There it is!
Sweet!
There it is! I got it!
The main thing... I did it...
It's delicious!
We went to the main course and had it!
I love the main course!
What is it? Kahori Paradise?
Cream paradise.
But I understand.
I can tell that it's so good it's a cream paradise.
It's true.
Okay, then.
It's so good.
It's amazing.
No water left in the ice cubes.
Yeah.
What did you do?
Wow!
That's superhuman.
Yes, sir.
How about you, Taka?
You scared the shit out of me.
Why?
He said he might have made a Motifkin.
Why did you make it?
I used to be an idol lover, and I met Akitagawa when I was in primary school,
From there, I was with Miki Hirose,
I met my staff, who liked idols.
And when we all fell in love with something together...
Is this your first time, or are you not interested?
I was just thinking that.
No, yeah.
I'm pretty sure...
It's like, one day there was this new girl who came to school. That girl was really...
She was like an angel.
She was really cute.
And,
wearing platinum.
And she cried a little bit.
We usually watch together.
I was looking at you guys too.
So, that's why.
And when I saw it...
I thought, "Oh, I really think we might be a bit alike".
That's when I started to like her.
That's when I decided to get to know you better.
I started liking Meimei-san.
I see.
This is the first time I've heard a story like this.
Such a story.
Wow.
Wow!
That's great.
Was I right?
Yes, it was.
It was even better than I imagined.
What?
Well, I'm glad.
It was like you made me say I'm happy.
Like I made you say you were happy.
Well, that's it for today's Bajkaho date, it was a lot of fun.
I'll miss you.
You're so cute when you say you're sad.
I can't go home.
You're so cute today, Uemei.
She's really been a big sister to me.
It's so different.
Really.
The proof is still there.
Not at all.
I want to date Kahorin again.
Come on.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, I want to go on a date with Alin, thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
It was a relaxing date with Alin.
Bye bye.
알림 설정